XAVIER DUVAL

Download PDF duvalx@free.fr

+0336912019

COMPUTER SCIENTIST, TEST AUTOMATION ENGINEER

Profile

Confirmed software developer mainly on the back office. Able to manage a project and a team on technical projects. Always smiling and interested in new technologies.

Skills

Design and Code Software

Expert in python language to

design and develop software.

Project Support Adaptability to provide project support and formation for any users of any level.

Project Direction

Proven ability to lead and manage a wide variety of design and development projects in team and independent situations.

Technical

Python	GitLab CI/CD	Robot Framework
Java	Jenkins	Behave
C++	Docker	PHP

Experience

WORLDLINE

Test automation engineer

2021-Now

Develop test automation framework for WORLDLINE payment solution on a payment electronic device, a point of sale and a payment server.

Develop servers simulators for several payment protocols. Develop a graphical interface and a simulator to use a payment card. Develop API and keywords to deal with payment electronic device.

INGENICO

2009-2021

Test automation engineer

Develop test automation framework for INGENICO payment solution on a payment electronic device, a point of sale and a payment server.

Installation of Gitlab runner for CI/CD.

SAGEM Mobile Phone

2006-2008

Integration engineer for embedded mobile software

Integration of SAGEM GSM mobile embedded software on a SONY ERICSSON platform.

ALCATEL Mobile Phone

2001-2006

Customization development for embedded mobile software.

Embedded software for customizing GSM and GPRS mobiles for different operators. Development, integration and updating of the tools of the DCG (Data Customization Group) service responsible for producing all the data for the basic embedded software of all ALCATEL mobiles and customizing them for all ALCATEL customer operators.

National Military Service

2000-2001

Logistics Department

Setting up an ORACLE database for the food production center

IBM GLOBAL SERVICES

1999

Solution Design Center

Development of Lotus Notes database administration tools to measure activity on the service's databases and to study the user profiles.

Paris North Computer Laboratory

1998-1999

Develops the graphical interface to visualize words according to their importance and their links and to allows the user to interact with these words and links.

Education

Paris XIII University

Graduate Diploma in Software Engineering